

#### PROJECT/PROGRAM MANAGER

12301 Silverstream Lane, Manor, Texas 78653

□+1 512 927 6286 | Seanryanholden@gmail.com | 🖬 seanryanholden

# **Summary**

Current Project Manager at Dell Technologies within Sales Services supporting global, backend developers and end users. Maintains sales and data analytics software through issue discovery, tracking, and collaboration with a focus on automation and the user experience. 5 years as a people leader and 3 years of overlapping project management experience, this is 6+ years in change leadership. Interested in discovering new skill sets and methods of collaboration while supporting a product that creates excitement as both a professional and consumer.

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

Dell Technologies Round Rock, Texas

ADVISOR, PROJECT/PROGRAM MANAGER

Jun 2021 - Present

- Identifies issues through data analytics, end user reporting, and pre-deployment testing, creating group discussions based on these findings with product managers, end users, and developers to **collaborate** and devise a path to completion with a focus on **prioritization**.
- Drives communication via virtual Zoom meetings, chat discussion via Teams and email, organization wide newsletters, all to ensure each involved party are consistently and accurately updated along with any associated issue in Jira and ServiceNow. Firm believer in the ideal that you can communicate effectively with anyone regardless of business or technical acumen if you take the time to hear them first.
- Monitors the progress of open issues and determines impact upon submission, e.g., a line attribute error in the order creation process could range from \$3K to \$30M of withheld revenue and require general issue creation or real-time stakeholder engagement through to issue resolution respectively. Monitoring continues post-resolution to ensure the feature release or deployed update is future proof.
- Runs scenarios in test environments for upcoming feature releases, deployments, or any change published by developers in a Task or Story to ensure there is no interruption or unforeseen change to the **user experience**, signing off on each and cascading results to the business.
- Creates ongoing metric reporting and compiles it in a way that the viewer, **from end user to vice president**, is able to absorb and understand it as it creates the road map set for end of quarter. Presents on this data in a weekly, multi-department business meeting.

Dell Technologies Round Rock, Texas

TECHNICAL SUPPORT MANAGER

Mar 2016 - Jun 2021

- Collaborated with PMO teams to design and lead high impact, business wide change, e.g., movement from general point of sale consumers to the creation of a team designed to support federal businesses, a sector not supported in the past.
- Oversaw piloting of federally regulated tools, created weekly reporting for PMO review, and presented to **director and vice president** level stakeholders. Led the design of a support model tailored for federal support and a workspace frontline would need to achieve this.
- Interviewed and onboarded **180+** new employees. Created and led a curriculum designed to turn even the most novice technology users into self-maintained IT personnel at the end of a three week period through in-class education, discussion, and job shadowing.
- Drove metric performance of each employee through analytics, external and internal feedback, and the review of cases created in Oracle post discovery via consumer chats and emails. This 24/7 team went on to outperform every other team **globally** for two consecutive years.
- · Received regional Top Performer and global Everyday Hero awards during this period as manager.

Dell Technologies Round Rock, Texas

SENIOR TECHNICIAN · TECHNICAL LEAD · TEAM LEAD

Oct 2012 - Mar 2016

- Supported the direct manager of each frontline team by providing real-time employee support, answering questions regarding process, policy, tool usage, anything to ensure that their often strenuous and difficult role assisting external end users included no internal roadblocks.
- Published new product, tool, and process change training, created through years of use and later assisting frontline employees. These documents were used during new employee training as well as included in our internal FAQ and knowledge base articles.
- Received regional **Top Performer** and **Significant Contributor** awards during this period as team lead.

### **Education**

#### **Collin County Community College**

GRAPHIC DESIGN, MUSIC BUSINESS

Plano, Texas

Aug 2008 - May 2010

• Focused on front end development and commercial media.

# **Extracurricular Activity**

Dell Technologies | Pride

Round Rock, Texas

CENTRAL TEXAS LIAISON

Oct 2016 - Present

- Promotes campus wide Pride awareness, an employee resource group, through newsletters educating on cross-company networking, charity events, ways to support the Austin local LGBTQIA+ community. Speaks at internal and external job fairs as a Pride liaison.
- Assists in and recruits others to help with the construction of a float each year for the Austin Pride parade.
- Presents to new employee training classes to deliver general information about Pride and other employee resource groups.